Guide to the Music Department records, 1898-2004 RG0075
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Programs and Publicity, 1961-2010; Series 11 (Map-folder 1)
  - GW Music Newsletter, 1996-2007, August 1996, November 2006, November 2007; Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Newsletter, 1998-2006; Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Newsletter Notes, 2008; Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Newsletter, 2008-2009; Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Scholarship Showcase, 1997; Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Year of the Flood Script, 2009; Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Democracy Press, 2005; Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Publicity, 2006-2007, Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Publicity, 2007-2008, Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Publicity, 2008-2009, Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Publicity, 2009-2010, Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Music Department Related Programs, 2006-2010, Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Department Related Clippings, 1982-2010; Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Troubadours poster -- Concert, Barcelona, Santa Maria del Pino, 29 May; RG0075 Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Poster -- Margaret Atwood Dramatic Reading with Music, 24 April 2010; RG0075 Series 11 (Map-folder 1, Poster 1)
  - Poster -- A Little Night Music, 9 March-11 March; RG0075 Series 11 (Map-folder 1, Poster 2)
  - Poster -- Fifth Varna International Conductors' Workshop, 26 May 2003; RG0075 Series 11 (Map-folder 1, Poster 3)
    Choral concert given by George Washington University Chamber Choir and the George Washington University Troubadours.
  - Poster -- George Washington University Troubadours concert, Czech Republic, May 1996; RG0075 Series 11 (Map-folder 1, Poster 4)
  - Poster -- George Washington University Troubadours concert, Firenze Fiorita, 13 May 1994; RG0075 Series 11 (Map-folder 1, Poster 5)
  - Poster -- George Washington University Chamber Choir concert, Russia, 27 May 2003; RG0075 Series 11 (Map-folder 1, Poster 6)
- Administrative Files, 1974-2009; Series 12
  This series contains administrative files for the Department of Music. They appear to have been the files of Deputy Chair of the Department of Music, Roy J. Guenther. Subjects include master classes and guest lectures, guest ensembles, faculty position requests, curriculum and program reviews, student competence subcommittee, performance committee, alumni surveys, faculty meetings, syllabi and course enrollments, equipment and facilities, student and faculty handbooks, and strategic plans. Materials date between 1974 and 2009, with the bulk of the material dating between 1990 and 2000.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Folders 48-54 are closed for 50 years from date of record creation. They contain personnel files, as well as information about faculty hiring.
  - Cleo Laine, October 1996; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Balint Sarosi lecture, September 1983; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Monty Alexander, Fall 1991; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Phyllis Bryn-Julson Master Class, 1991; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Music Facility Cluster, 1974-1983; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Barry Manilow Scholarship and C. Hagwood Photographs, 1984; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Pep Band Correspondence, 1984; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Coolidge Quartet [1/2], 2002; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Coolidge Quartet [2/2], 2002; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Joint Productions with Theater and Dance Department, 1993-1994; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Replacement Quartet in Residence, 2002; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Faculty position requests, 1989-1991; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Curriculum Review Committee; Voice, Piano, Violin, 1991; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Competence Subcommittee, 1990; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Performance Committee, 1990; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Survey, 1989; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Policy Archive, 1987-2000; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Canadian Brass at GW, 1994; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Performance Levels, Approved Requirements, 1996; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1992; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Curriculum Review, 1990; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Robert Parris, former faculty, 1999-2000; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Chair letter to faculty, August 2006; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Part-time Faculty Promotion, 1992-2004; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - George Steiner Obituaries, 2009; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - University Band Budget, 1996; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Portrait Bust of Dr. Robert H. Harmon, 2000; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Program Review, 1990; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - GSAS Music Review, 1983-1984; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Self Study, Program Review, 1998; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Chamber Players, Contract, Forms, 1994; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Music Department Faculty Meeting Notes, 1985-1989; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Music Department Faculty Meeting Notes, 1989-1997; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Syllabi, 2004; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Alum letter to band, 1997; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Choral Endowment, undated; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - BA Curriculum Review, 2002; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Course Enrollment, 1999-2003; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1996; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Faculty Handbook, July 1997; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Strategic Plan and Review, Spring 1998; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Student Handbook, Fall 2001; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Wish list, Five Year Plan, 1997; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Gospel Choir, 1997; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Department Planning Memos, 1987-1998; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Equipment and Space, 1998-1999; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - John Corigliano, 1998; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Keena Washington, 2008-2009; Series 12 (Box R1, Folder 1, Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Supplemental CVs, Self Study Strategic Plan 2004, Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 49, Box R1, Folder 2)
  - Kathleen Smith, 2007-2008; Series 12 (Box R1, Folder 3, Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Joti Rockwell, 2006-2007; Series 12 (Box R1, Folder 4, Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Jazz Studies Committee, 1991-1992; Series 12 (Box R1, Folder 5, Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Coolidge Quartet Resumes, 2001; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 53, Box R1, Folder 6)
  - Welling Professorship, 1994-1998; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 54, Box R1, Folder 7)
  - Self-Study Report: National Association of Schools of Music Accreditation Visit, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Student Files, 1970-2009; Series 13
  This series contains music student files. Documents pertain to course enrollment, grades, exams, and recitals, and date between 1970 and 2009.
  Access to student records is governed by the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which protects the privacy of student education records. Student records are closed for 100 years from date of record creation.
  - Ivison, Katharine, 1974; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dietrich, Joseph, 2007; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dunham, Charlotte, 1981; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Niederman, Brett, 2005; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Vaeth, Leslie, 2006; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Kantor, Jonathan, 2002-2006; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Wilkie, Joshua, 2006; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Wilson, David, 2006; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Retka, Jessica, 2008; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Maxman, Melissa, 1981; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Leeder, Aaron, 2005; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cookson, John, 1976; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Collura, Jacquie, 2003; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Caridi, Cristina, 2005; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Levor, Brian, 2005; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Caraviello, Roberta, 1973; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Coe, Mary, 1992; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Biggers, Robert, 1975; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Clark, C.D., 1997; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Conway, Dan, 1995; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Cruz, Catharine, 1998; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Blake, Eleanor, 2005; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Kaplan, Marc, 1987; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Lutz, Tim, 1979; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Kim, Hee Jung, 1999; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Kim, Jon, 1996; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Kleiner, Adam, 2002; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Lerman, Zena, 1975; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Chitty, Ismene, 1985-1994; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Marszal Kowsky, Paul, 2006; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Liberovsky, Maria, 2007; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Lintott, Robert, 2008; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Kuo, Stanley, 2007; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Yu, Andrew, 2008; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Thornewill, Benjamin, 2007; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Stalarow, Alex J., 2007; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Robertson, Emily, 2008; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Rollins, Gerri, 2006; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Holland, Caitlin, 2005; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Lee, Linda, 2005; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Lazar, Chad, 2000; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Darcey, Andrew, 2006; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Engelbrecht, Stephanie, 2006; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Bender, Scott, 2006; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Stern, Jeff, 2005; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Shyer, Evan, 2005; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Csatari, Alexandra, 2005; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Hovnanian, Karinne, 2008; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Hoffmann, Jennifer, 2007; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Hirsch, Rachel, 2007; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Young, Stephano, 1980-1987; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Post, Suzanne, 2006; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Guillot, Timothy, 2008; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Levy, James, 1993; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - McCarthy, Mary, 1993; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Mazer, Dan, 2000; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Wood, Eileen, 1972; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Wolpert, Thomas, 1972; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Harway, Sonya, 2002; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Hutchinson, Ruth, 1994; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Ito, Reona, 2000; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Henceroth, Judy, 1977; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Wood, Eric, 1981; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Hansen, Gwendolyn, 1979; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Harris, Ward, 1990; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - LaFauci, Kristin, 2000; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Fessenden, Jon, 2006; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Christie, William, 1981; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cooper, Karena, 1997; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Findley, Matt, 1993-1995; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Allen, Craig, 1997; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Allen, Denise N., 1992; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Farquharson, Bruce, 1999; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Faircloth, Diane, 1979-1986; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Guzman, Antonio de, 2000; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Anandanadesan, Rathai, 2003; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - DiTanna, Anthony, 1997; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Gintzig, Karen Ann, 1977; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Gilpin, Norma, 1973; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Giges, Melissa Heather, 1998; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Conforti, Jonathan, 1989; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Fine, Melissa, 1994; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Gappa, Judith, 1970; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Cardullo, Karen, 1979; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Garden, Helen, 1973; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Cappelletti, Sky, 1990; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Fox, Jeremy, 1987; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Cappelletti, Sky, 1984-1990; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Brown, Sarah, 2002; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Fox, Jeremy, 1984-1994; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Bader, Robert, 1988-1990; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Aycud, Imelda, 1985-1990; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Anderson, Sarah, 1993-1995; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Anderson, Charles, 1977-1979; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Eldridge, Jennifer, 1985-1990; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Dellario, Michael, 1973; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Bingham, John, 1976-1993; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Flom, Bethany, 2008; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Custer, Gerald, 1977-1979; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Perlmutter, Betsey, 2007; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Morgan, Jayna, 2003; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Dobry, Wallace, 1976; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Kane, Sara, 2006; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Laurito, Aaron, 2006; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Corica, Matt, 2007; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Daniels, Gordon, 2008; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Davis, Cory, 2008; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - DeCurtis, Daniel, 2007; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Yang, Hae-Ja, 1981-1991; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Cartwright, Douglass Anne, 2009; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Miller, Peter, 2008; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Marquardt, Melissa J., 2007; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Hee Jong Kim, 2000; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Helgert, Lars, 1997-2000; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Hill, Donald, 1978-1982; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Harmon, Melvin, 1976-1982; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Hong, Chung-won, 1986-1990; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Horvath, Sheera, 1991-1996; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Hildebrand, David, 1986; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Holler, Katie, 1987-1993; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Holck, Eric, 1985-1990; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Hribar, Dennis, 1978-1979; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Wyman, Chancellor, 1992-1997; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- National Association of Schools of Music, 1977-2005; 1985-1992; Series 14
  This series contains reports and surveys pertaining to the National Association of Schools of Music. Materials range in date from 1978 to 2005, with the bulk of the material dating between 1985 and 1992.
  - National Association of Schools of Music Report 1, 1 October 1996; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - National Association of Schools of Music Report 2, 1991-1996; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - National Association of Schools of Music Program Approvals, 1978-1986; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - National Association of Schools of Music Visitors Report, 1990; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Part-time Faculty Committee, 1990; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Institution Responses National Association of Schools of Music, October 1986; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - National Association of Schools of Music Self Study Report Spring 1985, Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - National Association of Schools of Music Self Study April 1990, Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - National Association of Schools of Music 1977, Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - National Association of Schools of Music Heads, 1997-1998, 1998-1999; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - National Association of Schools of Music Data Heads Surveys, 2004-2005; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - National Association of Schools of Music Reports, Fall 1992; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Self Study Report, 1985; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - National Association of Schools of Music Visit, April 1990; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - National Association of Schools of Music Visitors Report, 1990; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - National Association of Schools of Music Visit, 1985; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - National Association of Schools of Music Self Study, 1990; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - National Association of Schools of Music Visitation Report 1, 1990; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - National Association of Schools of Music Visitation Report 2, 1990; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - National Association of Schools of Music Institutional Procedures, 1984; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - National Association of Schools of Music Certificate, November 1979; RG0075 Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 1)